He's arrived in the St. Nick of time!
Santa with Muscles is a action, family, comedy film directed by John Murlowski.
A heartless millionaire believes he is Santa Claus
after an accident renders him amnesiac.
Blake, played by Hulk Hogan.
Ebner Frost, played by Ed Begley Jr..
Lenny, played by Don Stark.
Leslie, played by Robin Curtis.
Hinkley, played by Clint Howard.
Sarah, played by Mila Kunis.
Santa with Muscles is a 1996 American Christmas comedy film
starring Hulk Hogan and directed by John Murlowski.
It was released for two weeks in cinemas.
The film explores themes of amnesia, santa claus, millionaire, christmas.
The tone is lighthearted.